<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lilla Toma</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:47:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Travianer</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/travianer/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 15:47:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/travianer/</guid>
        <description>This is a Unity game project made with Unity 2022.3.13f1. This project was done with the collaboration of Viktória Horváth, who helped in many graphical, and coding assets of the project. The project is based on the web browser, war strategy game, Travian by Travian Games GmbH. Assets are reused from the original Travian project, and we do not own any of them. They are the intellectual property of Travian Games GmbH.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earn That Bread</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/earn-that-bread/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 17:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/earn-that-bread/</guid>
        <description>This game is an entry for the Mini Jam 94: Baking game jam. The game jam came with a limitation: You can only use 2 buttons.
The GitHub repository of the game can be found here:
GitHub repository The goal of this game is to bake an amount of bread that was ordered by the king. You need to get ingredients to bake bread, however on the way to collect them, you might run into some trouble.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chain Reaction</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/chain-reaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 16:10:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/chain-reaction/</guid>
        <description>Flat Chain Reaction is a remake of an Android game called Chain Reaction. The reason I wanted it to be remade is because the game used an interesting 3D grid that sometimes didn&amp;rsquo;t detect clicks properly, and I remade it in flat.
The GitHub repository of the game can be found here:
GitHub repository The game is a multiplayer strategy game, that people can play against friends. A player places little orbs on the map.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cell Wars</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/cell-wars/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 15:47:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/cell-wars/</guid>
        <description>Cell Wars was basically my first game project, written in C++, based on the concept of the game called Phage Wars. Cell Wars is a singleplayer, territory-control strategy game where the players goal is to be the only &amp;ldquo;organism&amp;rdquo; in the cells presented on the playfield.
This project was started and finished in 2019, in roughly 1 or 2 weeks, I don&amp;rsquo;t remember exactly.
To briefly display, what the game has to offer, here are a few links:</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pumpkin Attack</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/pumpkin-attack/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 15:47:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/pumpkin-attack/</guid>
        <description>This game was made as a challenge to myself. I wanted to see if I could create a game in a single day, more specifically in 8 hours. Unfortunately I failed, because I still needed an extra 4-ish hours to finish this project.
The game is themed on Halloween day, where a kid is left out in a small suburban neighborhood, and he has to collect baskets of candies. However, he is attacked by zombies, witches and jumping pumpkins.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DaiCastle</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/daicastle/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 15:47:30 +0200</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/daicastle/</guid>
        <description>DaiCastle is a singleplayer, 100-player battle-royale game with a huge map, complex AI, inventory system, unlockable item system, replay system, and many more.
This project was started in 2019, most of the core things were done back then such as the way the map is shown, and stored, hit-reg calculations, movements, but then I had to discontinue this project unfortunately.
In 2021, I revisited the project, and started adding many new features, that now makes the game full.</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>